Guide to the Riggs Family papers, 1672-2006 MS2239
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Riggs Family papers
1672-1987
1870-1939
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Riggs, Miriam Ely
Riggs, John Beverley
MS2239
36.5 Linear Feet
This collection contains family photographs (including daguerreotypes and tintypes), travel photographs, books, artwork, personal accessories, draft manuscripts, newspaper clippings, and correspondence. The materials date from 1672-2006, with the bulk of the collection ranging from 1870-1939. The records are related to the Riggs family, including Thomas Riggs, territorial governor of Alaska (1918-1921), and family members involved with the Riggs National Bank of Washington, D.C. Family historian John Beverley Riggs amassed these materials and gave them to his niece Miriam Ely Riggs.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Series
Organized into 3 series: Photographs and prints, Personal artifacts, and Paper documents.
Acquisition Information
Purchased from Miriam Ely Riggs 2007 (Accession 2007.60). Gift of Miriam Ely Riggs 2007 (Accession 2007.75) (Accession 2007.76).
Historical or Biographical Note
John Beverley Riggs (1918-2006), author, curator, archivist, and historian, gathered the materials in this collection. He graduated from The George Washington University in 1939, and later attended Yale, writing his doctoral dissertation on "The Acquisition of Foreign Archival Sources for American History to the Year 1949" in 1955. His published works include The Riggs Family of Maryland: A Genealogical and Historical Record (1939), Documentary Sources for Historic Preservation: Manuscripts (1964), A Guide to the Manuscripts in the Eleutherian Mills Historical Library (1978), as well as studies of early Maryland landowners and society.
The members of the Riggs family represented in this collection include three of the sons of businessman and banker Elisha Riggs, Sr. (1779-1853): George Washington Riggs, Jr. (1813-1881), partner in Corcoran and Riggs; Lawrason Riggs (1814-1884); and Elisha Riggs, Jr. (1826-1881), another partner in Corcoran and Riggs (which became Riggs & Co. in 1854).
George Washington Riggs, Jr.'s son Elisha Francis Riggs, Sr. (1851-1910) became a partner of Riggs & Co. in 1876 and remained involved until 1896, when the bank incorporated to become the public Riggs National Bank; he married Medora Thayer Riggs (1852-1915) and had three sons: George Washington Riggs, Jr. (1880-1883), who died in infancy; Elisha Francis Riggs, Jr. (1887-1936), who served in the U.S. Army; and Thomas Lawrason Riggs (1888-1943), who served as a medic in World War I and was later ordained a priest.
Also represented in the collection are Thomas Riggs, Jr. (1873-1945), another Riggs family member and governor of Alaska from 1918-1921, his wife Renee Coudert Riggs (1892-?), and their son Thomas (Tommy) Riggs Jr. (1915-1953).
Other Finding Aids
Please see the PNC-Riggs Bank Collection for business records. http://www.gwu.edu/gelman/spec/ead/ms2239.xml
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains family photographs (including daguerreotypes and tintypes), travel photographs, books, artwork, personal accessories, draft manuscripts, newspaper clippings, and correspondence. The materials date from 1672-2006, with the bulk of the collection ranging from 1870-1939. The records are related to the Riggs family, including Thomas Riggs, territorial governor of Alaska (1918-1921), and family members connected to the Riggs National Bank of Washington, D.C. However, there are no materials that discuss the business affairs of the Riggs Bank (Please see the PNC-Riggs Bank Collection for business records).
The Thomas Riggs material contains family photographs in Alaska from 1914-1925, newspaper clippings relating to his governorship, and some business correspondence from 1922-1947.
Photographs include portraits of Riggs family members, particularly E. Francis Riggs Sr. and his children, and are prevalent in both framed and unframed formats. Travel photographs represent the late nineteenth century Middle East and Asia, early twentieth century Europe, a U.S. cross-country trip, and World War II in North Africa.
The draft manuscripts consist of multiple drafts of "The Riggs Family of Maryland: a Genealogical and Historical Record" by John Beverley Riggs and a single draft of "Remarks on Some of the Oldest Maps in America" by Frederic Kunstmann.
Riggs genealogy is recorded in the seventeenth century "Baxter's Christian Directory" and in John Beverley Riggs' draft manuscripts of "The Riggs Family of Maryland."
Black-and-white photographs; Alaska; Middle East -- Pictorial works; Alaska -- Pictorial works; Photographs; Cabinet photographs; Ambrotypes; Card photographs (photographs); Daguerreotypes (photographs); Carte-de-visite (card photographs); Cased photographs; Riggs, Miriam Ely; Riggs family; Riggs, George Washington; Riggs, Thomas; Riggs, Elisha Francis; Riggs, Elisha
- Photographs and prints, circa 1800 - circa 1948; Series 1; 15.75 Linear Feet
  Arrangement
  Arranged by format type.
  Scope and Contents
  Photographs and prints include framed photographs, ambrotypes, tintypes, Daguerreotypes, unframed photographs on paper, landscape prints, and photo albums. The bulk of the material dates between 1877-1943. Portraits and travel photographs are represented. Portraits primarily depict Riggs family members, particularly E. Francis Riggs Sr. and his children, and are prevalent in both framed and unframed formats. Travel photographs represent the late nineteenth and early twentieth century Middle East and Asia, early twentieth century Europe, a U.S. cross-country trip, and World War II in North Africa.
  - Riggs Relatives Photos, circa 1862-1913; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Elisha Francis Riggs Sr. Photos, circa 1870; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Elisha Francis Riggs Sr. and Medora Thayer Riggs Photos, circa 1877- circa 1890; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Riggs Relatives Photos, circa 1877- circa 1925; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - EFR-Snapshots and Home Photos, circa 1895; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Riggs Relatives Photos, circa 1900; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Photos-Wm. Henry Riggs, circa 1900; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Thomas Riggs Jr., Governor of Alaska Photos, circa 1919- circa 1927; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Some Riggs Women Photos, undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Unidentified people, undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Unidentified people, undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Hand colored portraits and photos of babies of EFR, Sr. (EFR Jr., TLR, & GWR Jr.), circa 1881; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Elisha Francis Riggs, Jr. and Thomas Lawrason Riggs baby photos, circa 1889; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Elisha Francis Riggs, Jr. and Thomas Lawrason Riggs, circa 1889; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Elisha Francis Riggs, Jr. and Thomas Lawrason Riggs Photographs, circa 1889- circa 1892; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Elisha Francis Riggs, Jr. and Thomas Lawrason Riggs Photographs, circa 1899- circa 1902; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Elisha Francis Riggs, Jr. and Thomas Lawrason Riggs Photographs, circa 1899- circa 1919; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Possibly Elisha Francis Riggs, Jr. and Thomas Lawrason Riggs, circa 1900- circa 1910; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Elisha Francis Riggs Jr. and Thomas Lawrason Riggs, photos as adults, circa 1910- circa 1940; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - E.F. Riggs Jr.-Military Photos, circa 1911- circa 1919; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Elisha Francis Riggs Jr. Military and other, circa 1911- circa 1919; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Elisha Francis Riggs, Jr. Military Photos, 1913-1914; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Thomas Lawrason Riggs, unidentified people, and travel photos (all in one set) [1/2], circa 1916- circa 1943; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Thomas Lawrason Riggs, unidentified people, and travel photos (all in one set) [2/2], circa 1916- circa 1943; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Three pictures of horses, on long cardboard, undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 1)
  - E.F.R. Green Hill 1925, Series 1 (Box 4, Item 2)
  - Bride, in paper folder, undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 3)
  - Woman with long pearl necklace, in paper folder, 1925; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 4)
  - Priest seated on couch (TLR?), in paper folder, undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 5)
  - House, undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 6)
  - Military group portrait, hats on, undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 7)
  - Military group portrait, hats off, undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 8)
  - Man in uniform, undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 9)
  - Asian garden, 1874; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 10)
  - Asian house, 1874; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 11)
  - Tree in center, veranda on right, woman and man seated, two men standing, undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 12)
  - Trees, with woman walking in center, undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 13)
  - Doorway of Asian house, multiple people outside, undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 14)
  - Two horse carriages with people, in front of house, undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 15)
  - View down dirt road, buildings and trees, undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 16)
  - "Side of house looking south…", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 17)
  - "Back of the house…", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 18)
  - Outdoor picture with man on horse, two children in baskets on horse, three men standing by, undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 19)
  - "Greek Priests", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 20)
  - "Emir Mulhain Govener of the Druses", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 21)
  - "Arabs of Syria", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 22)
  - "Kurdes (Persians)", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 23)
  - "Patriach of Jerusalem (ordinary costume)", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 24)
  - "Patriach of Jerusalem (special costume)", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 25)
  - "Patriach of the Marometes (Ordinary Costume)", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 26)
  - "Druse Cavalry", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 27)
  - "Inhabitants of Alexandria", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 28)
  - "No. 26 Bourgeoise de Cairo-Costume de Ville", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 29)
  - "Druse Senators", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 30)
  - "Arabs of Marocua" (?), undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 31)
  - "Bedouins", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 32)
  - "Syrians", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 33)
  - "…Lady of Bank", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 34)
  - "Princes of the Druses", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 35)
  - "Greek Bishop", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 36)
  - "Diacres of the Greek Church", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 37)
  - "Nendecan Dervish" (?), undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 38)
  - "Arabs of Gaza", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 39)
  - "Nubian Warrior", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 40)
  - "Greeks", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 41)
  - "Kavar du Council de fiance"(?), undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 42)
  - "Nubians 1st cataract", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 43)
  - "Effendis", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 44)
  - "Patriach of the Nurometes (Special costume)", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 45)
  - "Arabian Musicians", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 46)
  - "Derish Turners", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 47)
  - "Jewess of Damascus", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 48)
  - "Arabian Café", undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Item 49)
  - Ambrotype of an unidentified girl, undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Tintype of Elisha Francis Riggs Jr. and William Coleman Rogers, 09\30\1903; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Tintype of Elisha Francis Riggs Jr. and Chester J. Cofmann, 1904; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Tintype of Elisha Francis Riggs Jr., circa 1908- circa 1909; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Tintype of Elisha Francis Riggs and Medora Thayer Riggs, undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Tintype of five unidentified people in a car, undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Tintype of two unidentified boys, undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Tintype of two unidentified women, undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Medora Thayer Riggs, silver frame, undated; Series 1 (Box 6, Item 1)
  - Unidentified man behind desk, wooden frame, undated; Series 1 (Box 6, Item 2)
  - EFR Jr military, with woman, undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Item 1)
  - EFR Jr military, with two unidentified uniformed men, undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Item 2)
  - unidentified woman and child, undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Item 3)
  - EFR Sr with sons EFR Jr and TLR, undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Item 4)
  - EFR Jr and TLR as boys, undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Item 5)
  - Unidentified man, undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Item 6)
  - Unidentified woman, seated, undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Item 7)
  - Unidentified man wearing bow tie, undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Item 8)
  - Unidentified Native American, undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Item 9)
  - Two boys in costume, EFR Jr and TLR?, undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Item 10)
  - "Westminster School, ? Conn. Students: E.F. Riggs 1902-5, T. L Riggs 1903-6", undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Item 11)
  - EFR Sr with sons EFR Jr and TLR, undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Item 12)
  - Two boys in hats outdoors, probably EFR Jr and TLR, undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Item 13)
  - "1311 Mass. Ave. Residence of E. Francis Riggs. Built about 1886.", undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Item 14)
  - Unidentified woman, seated, in dress, undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Item 15)
  - House, "'Fareham', New London, …", undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Item 16)
  - Snowy mountain,"0-13-3-06", undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Item 17)
  - Mountain, "0-17-6-06", undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Item 18)
  - Mountains, "0-17-5-06", undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Item 19)
  - Snowy mountains, "0-13-2-06", undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Item 20)
  - "The Vigil of the Ages, Scarborough, Alaska", undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Item 21)
  - "Kenny Lake Roadhouse, Chitino-Fairbanks Trail, Alaska, Scarborough", undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Item 22)
  - Franklin Delano Roosevelt, autographed photo, black frame, undated; Series 1 (Box 8, Item 1)
  - Unidentified child with toy horse, framed, undated; Series 1 (Box 8, Item 2)
  - Unidentified man in suit, frame stand loose, undated; Series 1 (Box 8, Item 3)
  - Unidentified woman, undated; Series 1 (Box 10)
  - Unidentified woman, undated; Series 1 (Box 10)
  - Man in glasses, undated; Series 1 (Box 10)
  - Boy in uniform, undated; Series 1 (Box 10)
  - Boy in hat, undated; Series 1 (Box 10)
  - Man in suit, undated; Series 1 (Box 10)
  - Unidentified man, black wood frame, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Item 1)
  - Unidentified man in uniform, wood frame, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Item 2)
  - 1912 travel photos, probably taken by Thomas Lawrason Riggs, photo album, Series 1 (Box 12, Item 1)
  - 1901-1904, New Haven and Elsewhere, photo album by EFR, Series 1 (Box 12, Item 2)
  - R.C.R. photo album, 1897- "Robin Vale Duer Pond." 1922- "Uncle, V. & Dikkl.", 1897-1922; Series 1 (Box 12, Item 3)
  - Governor Riggs family photo album: Thomas & Renee Riggs, their two children: Elizabeth (Lisette) Catherine Riggs (b. 3/26/1914) and Thomas Riggs (b. 12/25/1915), circa 1925; Series 1 (Box 13, Item 1)
  - Governor Riggs family photo album: Views of Washington DC, NJ, WA, Alaska, 1914-1916; Series 1 (Box 13, Item 2)
  - Governor Riggs family photo album: in Alaska, circa 1919; Series 1 (Box 13, Item 3)
  - Photo album: Europe, by Thomas Lawrason Riggs(?), circa 1916; Series 1 (Box 14, Item 1)
  - Photo album: Asia, by Thomas Lawrason Riggs(?), circa 1916; Series 1 (Box 15, Item 1)
  - Photo album: Thomas Riggs, Jr. in WWII: surrender of Tunisia, North African battles, circa 1943; Series 1 (Box 16, Item 1)
  - Photo album: cross country trip, including the midwest and west (Yellowstone, Utah, Niagara Falls, Gardner Montana), undated; Series 1 (Box 16, Item 2)
  - Framed portrait: Ellen Karick Burche, April 1828, Series 1 (Box 23, Object 5)
  - Framed portrait: EFR Sr, undated; Series 1 (Box 23, Object 7)
  - Framed portrait: unknown girl, black oval frame, undated; Series 1 (Box 23, Object 8)
  - Framed portrait: unknown woman, enamel frame, undated; Series 1 (Box 23, Object 9)
  - Framed portrait: unknown girl, silver frame, undated; Series 1 (Box 23, Object 10)
  - Framed portrait: unknown woman, standing, undated; Series 1 (Box 23, Object 11)
  - Framed portrait: unknown man, undated; Series 1 (Box 23, Object 12)
  - Glass frame: unknown man and boy, undated; Series 1 (Box 23, Object 13)
  - Glass frame: 2 unknown children, undated; Series 1 (Box 23, Object 14)
  - Glass frame: unknown woman, undated; Series 1 (Box 23, Object 15)
  - Purple velvet frame: unknown woman, undated; Series 1 (Box 23, Object 16)
  - Blue case: Renee Coudert Riggs, undated; Series 1 (Box 23, Object 17)
  - Red case: double portrait unknown man and woman, undated; Series 1 (Box 23, Object 18)
  - Glass frame: unknown girl, undated; Series 1 (Box 23, Object 19)
  - Daguerreotype: two unknown children, undated; Series 1 (Box 23, Object 20)
  - Daguerreotype: unidentified man and woman, undated; Series 1 (Box 23, Object 21)
  - Daguerreotype: unidentified man, undated; Series 1 (Box 23, Object 22)
  - Daguerreotype: unidentified man, undated; Series 1 (Box 23, Object 23)
  - Daguerreotype: unidentified child, undated; Series 1 (Box 23, Object 24)
  - Daguerreotype: unidentified woman, undated; Series 1 (Box 23, Object 25)
  - Portrait: Renee Condert Riggs, undated; Series 1 (Box 23, Object 26)
  - Framed portrait: unidentified woman, oval brass frame, undated; Series 1 (Box 23, Object 27)
  - Portrait: EFR Sr., silver frame with green velvet back, undated; Series 1 (Box 23, Object 28)
  - Painted portrait in case: unidentified man, undated; Series 1 (Box 24, Object 1)
  - Framed photograph: unidentified man in hammock, undated; Series 1 (Box 24, Object 2)
  - Framed photographs: three oval frames fused together, undated; Series 1 (Box 24, Object 3)
  - Framed photograph, broken frame, undated; Series 1 (Box 24, Object 4)
  - Framed photograph: unidentified girl holding "Sunnyside" book, undated; Series 1 (Box 24, Object 8)
  - U.S. landscape prints, undated; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - John Beverley Riggs in Okinawa, Japan during World War II [1 of 6], circa 1945; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    Some photographs are labeled on the backside.
  - John Beverley Riggs in Okinawa, Japan during World War II [2 of 6], circa 1945; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - John Beverley Riggs in Okinawa, Japan during World War II [3 of 6], circa 1945; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - John Beverley Riggs in Okinawa, Japan during World War II [4 of 6], circa 1945; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - John Beverley Riggs in Okinawa, Japan during World War II [5 of 6], circa 1945; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - John Beverley Riggs in Okinawa, Japan during World War II [6 of 6], circa 1945; Series 1 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - John Beverley Riggs Caribbean voyage photos [1 of 2], 1948; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - John Beverley Riggs Caribbean voyage photos [2 of 2], 1948; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Thomas Lawrason Riggs - dramatic and others [1 of 3], circa 1903; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Thomas Lawrason Riggs - dramatic and others [2 of 3], circa 1903- circa 1904; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Thomas Lawrason Riggs - dramatic and others [3 of 3], circa 1903- circa 1904; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Green Hill photos - home of Elisha F. Riggs, Jr., undated; Series 1 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Woolley photo and others from Yale Theatre Department, circa 1910; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Grave of Elisha Francis Riggs - Puerto Rico, 1936; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Portrait of four unknown children, undated; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Gilbertsville - family portrait, 1880 August 17; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Riggs family home, 1920 June 2; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Photos of interest, undated; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Negatives of Riggs family, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    Includes negatives of Mattie Ould (cousin of Riggs family), Elliot Riigs (1867), E. Riggs (New York, 1843 August 3), and George Washington Riggs.
  - Photo album - Thomas Lawrason Riggs in Europe and U.S.A., 1916; Series 1 (Box 55, Item 1)
  - Photo album - Riggs family, 1909-1921; Series 1 (Box 56, Item 1)
  - Photo album - Riggs family, 1902-1904; Series 1 (Box 57, Item 1)
  - Photographic printing plate of George Washington Riggs, undated; Series 1 (Box SHARED Box 22, Box 58, Item 1)
  - Photo album labeled with intials C.S.P. and C.C.J., 1938; Series 1 (Box 59, Item 1)
  - Unidentified people in costume, circa 1900; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified people in costume, circa 1900; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Unidentified people in costume, circa 1900; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Portrait of W. Vincent Wallace, 1936; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Photograph of church altar, circa 1900; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Portrait of Thomas Lawrason Riggs, circa 1900; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Portrait of Thomas Lawrason Riggs, circa 1900; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Unidentified boy in costume, 1903; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Unidentified people in costume, circa 1900; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Unidentified people in costume, circa 1900; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Unidentified people in costume, circa 1900; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Photograph of part of Colonel Elisha Francis Riggs command - Fort Riley, Kansas, 1912; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Glass plate negative: portrait of unidentified woman, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 61, Item 1)
  - Glass plate negative: portrait of Mary J. Bright, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 61, Item 2)
    Wife of Lawrason Riggs.
  - Glass plate negative: portrait of unidentified man and woman, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 61, Item 3)
  - Glass plate negative: portrait of unidentified woman and two girls, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 61, Item 4)
  - Glass plate negative: portrait of unidentified woman, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 61, Item 5)
  - Glass plate negative: portrait of boy with dogs, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 61, Item 6)
  - Glass plate negative: house, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 61, Item 7)
  - Glass plate negative: dog on leash, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 61, Item 8)
  - Glass plate negative: two unidentified men on horseback, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 61, Item 9)
  - Glass plate negative: portrait of unidentified man, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 62, Item 1)
    This glass plate negative is either cracked or broken.
  - Glass plate negative: portrait of unidentified man, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 62, Item 2)
  - Glass plate negative: house, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 62, Item 3)
  - Glass plate negative: dog on leash, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 62, Item 4)
  - Glass plate negative: portrait of unidentified man, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 62, Item 5)
  - Glass plate negative: portrait of Lawrason Riggs, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 62, Item 6)
  - Glass plate negative: portrait of George W. Riggs, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 63, Item 1)
  - Glass plate negative: portrait of Elisha Riggs, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 63, Item 2)
  - Glass plate negative: unidentified group in front of house, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 63, Item 3)
  - Glass plate negative: unidentified group portrait, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 63, Item 4)
  - Glass plate negative: portrait of Elisha Riggs, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 63, Item 5)
  - Glass plate negative: portrait of Samuel Riggs, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 63, Item 6)
  - Glass plate negative: portrait of Mrs. Lawrason Riggs, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 63, Item 7)
  - Glass plate negative: portrait of unidentified woman, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 63, Item 8)
  - Glass plate negative: portrait of Alice Lawrason Riggs, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 64, Item 1)
    Wife of Elisha Riggs.